sketchpad.net 2011-05-25

# Mike's Sketchpad - Privacy Policy

  |  |  | 

Mike's Sketchpad  
Privacy Policy  
  
---|---  
  
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/faqs.asp).

**This website collects cookies.** ([Definition of Cookies](http://www.netlingo.com/right.cfm?term=cookies)) **  
** As you navigate through most websites, certain non-personally identifiable information may be collected automatically. Examples of this non-personally identifiable information include the name of your internet service provider, the website that you used to link to this website, the websites that you visit from this website and your IP-Address. This data could possibly lead to your identification; however it is not collected or used for this purpose. The data is used for statistical purposes, but the individual user remains anonymous.

**Google AdSense and the**[DoubleClick DART cookie](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx):

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. 
  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. 
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).
